<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>polychromos - Tag - Mark Cheret - Maker. Artist. Sculptor.</title><link>https://cheret.org/tags/polychromos/</link><description>polychromos - Tag - Mark Cheret - Maker. Artist. Sculptor.</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under the MIT License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 10:45:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cheret.org/tags/polychromos/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hearts on Fire</title><link>https://cheret.org/2022/10/hearts-on-fire/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 10:45:00 +0100</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.org/2022/10/hearts-on-fire/</guid><description>Input This Hearts on Fire project started as a study I sketched of a heart. I envisioned it to be an intricate piece with loads of details.
The original piece was created layering a bunch of colours. What started as a sketch with thin lines and a mis-shaped heart quickly turned into something a bit more clunky. However, I started to take a liking to this happy accident and decided to roll with it, adding further shades into the mix and extending the borders of the heart further and further.</description></item><item><title>Princess, Queen &amp; Goddess</title><link>https://cheret.org/2022/10/princess-queen-goddess/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 17:37:00 +0200</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.org/2022/10/princess-queen-goddess/</guid><description>This project is only one piece of an ongoing larger creative framing.
There will be an article on my coaching website about my theory of the origins of sexual attraction. It&amp;rsquo;s all about the polarity both in the expression of masculinity versus femininity as well as the components of healed versus wounded and how the magnitude of this magnetic force is amplified by how far removed from a central pole both parties are.</description></item><item><title>Art supply craze</title><link>https://cheret.org/2022/09/art-supply-craze/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 19:28:00 +0200</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.org/2022/09/art-supply-craze/</guid><description>The art supply craze has officially begun. I&amp;rsquo;m all in learning to work with colour and find creative expression using blank sheets of paper and some pencils. I massively fell in love with the handling and colour of the Polychromos colour pencils and discovered them as a fantastic tool for an artist. So I went and got myself a beautiful extension to the palette of available colours and some tools for sketching for my kid.</description></item><item><title>Sketchbook: Rainbow, Dark forest &amp; Double stars</title><link>https://cheret.org/2022/09/sketchbook-rainbow-dark-forest-double-stars/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 23:03:00 +0200</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.org/2022/09/sketchbook-rainbow-dark-forest-double-stars/</guid><description>This is my first drawing entry for my sketchbook. I&amp;rsquo;m sharing my progress as an artist publicly as a function of accountability for myself.
Being inspired to pick up drawing by an idea for a collage that came to my head while I was in deep thought about present and future of my love relationship, I went out and bought some top quality art supplies to fuel the creative process.</description></item></channel></rss>