<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>All Posts - Mark Cheret - Maker. Artist. Sculptor.</title><link>https://cheret.org/posts/</link><description>All Posts | Mark Cheret - Maker. Artist. Sculptor.</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under the MIT License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 19:28:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cheret.org/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Art supply craze</title><link>https://cheret.org/2022/09/art-supply-craze/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 19:28:00 +0200</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.org/2022/09/art-supply-craze/</guid><description>The art supply craze has officially begun. I&amp;rsquo;m all in learning to work with colour and find creative expression using blank sheets of paper and some pencils. I massively fell in love with the handling and colour of the Polychromos colour pencils and discovered them as a fantastic tool for an artist. So I went and got myself a beautiful extension to the palette of available colours and some tools for sketching for my kid.</description></item><item><title>Sketchbook: Rainbow, Dark forest &amp; Double stars</title><link>https://cheret.org/2022/09/sketchbook-rainbow-dark-forest-double-stars/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 23:03:00 +0200</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.org/2022/09/sketchbook-rainbow-dark-forest-double-stars/</guid><description>This is my first drawing entry for my sketchbook. I&amp;rsquo;m sharing my progress as an artist publicly as a function of accountability for myself.
Being inspired to pick up drawing by an idea for a collage that came to my head while I was in deep thought about present and future of my love relationship, I went out and bought some top quality art supplies to fuel the creative process.</description></item><item><title>Functional Sculpture: Podium</title><link>https://cheret.org/2021/05/functional-sculpture-podium/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 09:47:17 +0200</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.org/2021/05/functional-sculpture-podium/</guid><description>This podium is a functional sculpture. It was fashioned Bricolage-style from the scraps of building an original sound stage frame made out of 100x100mm pieces of spruce construction wood and a panel from an IKEA shelf system.
I thought of the concept, collected the material and a carpenter friend of mine assembled the pieces, making use of his woodworking equipment, which I didn&amp;rsquo;t have at the time. The foot is made out of 4 wood pieces of equal length, bolted together in pairs.</description></item><item><title>Popcorn Science Update</title><link>https://cheret.org/2021/04/popcorn-science-update/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 18:25:49 +0000</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.org/2021/04/popcorn-science-update/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>Some call me the &ldquo;Popcorn Pope&rdquo;. My popcorn creations are imaginative, tasty and far from the plain old bland popped corn.</p>
<p>So, to take you with me on this marvellous journey, I registered a domain on 18/09/2019 called popcorn-science.com. I&rsquo;m giving you a teaser here.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>my take on the Brexit</title><link>https://cheret.org/2016/06/my-take-on-the-brexit/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2016 21:04:11 +0000</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.org/2016/06/my-take-on-the-brexit/</guid><description><![CDATA[In the wake of the recent referendum of the United Kingdom&rsquo;s membership of the European Union which in short was just called &ldquo;Brexit&rdquo; for those in favour of leaving the EU, there has been a lot of buzz online and elsewhere. This of course was to be expected of a vote with the potential of having wide ranging consequences. I&rsquo;d like to call a lot of what&rsquo;s been going on merely &ldquo;noise&rdquo; while trying to distil the essence of it which I&rsquo;d like to call &ldquo;signal&rdquo;.]]></description></item><item><title>LBPC#042 - Bergmuffel</title><link>https://cheret.org/2015/06/lbpc-042-bergmuffel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2015 15:27:44 +0100</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.org/2015/06/lbpc-042-bergmuffel/</guid><description>LBPC#042 - Bergmuffel Die geilsten Berge der Welt vor der Nase und fast nie oben?
Shownotes Wir leben im Alpenvorland da leben und arbeiten wo andere Urlaub machen wie oft sind wir eigentlich auf den Bergen? einschlafen in der Badewanne Die Moar Alm auf der wir vor einem Monat waren ist hier von uns verfilmt worden:
Teilnehmer: Mark Cheret und Samuel Antosch</description></item><item><title>LBPC#041 - Medien nicht Marketing</title><link>https://cheret.org/2015/05/lbpc-041-medien-nicht-marketing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2015 15:27:44 +0100</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.org/2015/05/lbpc-041-medien-nicht-marketing/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="lbpc041---medien-nicht-marketing">LBPC#041 - Medien nicht Marketing&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Kommunikation der eigenen Marke, des eigenen Produktes oder der eigenen Dienstleistung&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>LBPC#040 – Rest in Peace Paul Walker</title><link>https://cheret.org/2015/05/lbpc-040-rip-paul-walker/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2015 22:39:44 +0100</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.org/2015/05/lbpc-040-rip-paul-walker/</guid><description>LBPC#040 - RIP Paul Walker Shownotes endlich ein neues Intro Jingle Vocoder vs. Autotune der emotional schwierige und gleichzeitig ironische Abgang von Paul Walker Amehra das erste mal auf einem Pferd Teilnehmer: Mark Cheret und Samuel Antosch</description></item><item><title>LBPC#039 - Social Media</title><link>https://cheret.org/2015/04/lbpc-039-social-media/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2015 13:23:43 +0100</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.org/2015/04/lbpc-039-social-media/</guid><description>Social Media. Welchen Mehrwert muss ich als Firma bieten? LBPC#039 - Social Media Shownotes Im Gespräch mit Marketing-Experten Christian Reiweger, BA, gehen wir der Frage auf den Grund, was der allseits geforderte aber nie genauer erklärte &amp;ldquo;Mehrwert&amp;rdquo; der Social-Media-Kanäle sein könnte, den die Firmen mit ihren Produkt-, Marken- oder Unternehmens-pages bieten sollen. Muss eine Firma überhaupt auf Facebook oder nicht? Ist es gut, wenn der Chef persönlich posted? Stelle ich jemanden ein oder beauftrage eine Agentur?</description></item><item><title>LBPC#038 – Selbstständigkeit</title><link>https://cheret.org/2015/04/lbpc-038-selbststaendigkeit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2015 13:23:43 +0100</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.org/2015/04/lbpc-038-selbststaendigkeit/</guid><description>Ein Gespräch mit Online Shop Betreiber Christian LBPC#038 – Selbstständigkeit Shownotes Wir erläutern aus eigener Erfahrung die Einstiegsvoraussetzungen und Hürden für die Selbstständigkeit, auch die Belohnung im Erfolgsfall, aber auch über die Motivation. Dazu noch eine ernst gemeinte Bitte an alle in Führungspositionen, sich auch um den emotionalen Part seiner Mitarbeiter zu kümmern, um gutes Personal halten zu können. Christian betreibt zusammen mit seiner Geschäftspartnerin einen Online Shop namens Pink Leaf für Rockabilly, Steampunk, Burlesque und Vintage Kleider.</description></item></channel></rss>