<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>development on cheret.org</title><link>https://cheret.org/tags/development/</link><description>Recent content in development on cheret.org</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 02:07:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cheret.org/tags/development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>footnotes</title><link>https://cheret.org/footnotes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 02:07:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cheret.org/footnotes/</guid><description>This page is about the WordPress plugin footnotes It has been under development since 19 March 2014.
footnotes aims to be the all-in-one solution for displaying an automatically generated list of references on your Page or Post. The Plugin ships with a set of defaults while also empowering you to control how your footnotes are being displayed.
footnotes gives you the ability to display well-formatted footnotes on your WordPress Pages and Posts — those footnotes we know from offline publishing.</description></item><item><title>My first post with a new CMS</title><link>https://cheret.org/2021/03/my-first-post-with-a-new-cms/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 15:36:53 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cheret.org/2021/03/my-first-post-with-a-new-cms/</guid><description>after more than a decade Just so you know, I&amp;rsquo;ve been a WordPress user, admin, and plugin author for more than a decade now. I could&amp;rsquo;ve set this up as yet another one of those ubiquitous WordPress pages. This time, however, I&amp;rsquo;m taking a different approach. HUGO is my tool of choice as I&amp;rsquo;m a DevSecOps Advisor, leaning into Infrastructure as Code (IaC) and of course the automation behind this declarative setup.</description></item><item><title>footnotes: How to recover from a crashing website</title><link>https://cheret.org/2021/03/footnotes-how-to-recover-from-a-crashing-website/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 02:17:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cheret.org/2021/03/footnotes-how-to-recover-from-a-crashing-website/</guid><description>Dear footnotes community,
We recently accidentally shipped a version of our plugin that might break your website. Apologising here.
How to recover from a crashing website? Fellow footnotes user @pppierreee pointed out that it would be helpful to give you guidance how to recover:
– Download footnotes 2.5.8 – Unzip – Delete the wp-content/plugins/footnotes/ folder on your webserver – Upload the contents of the unzip (the footnotes folder) to wp-content/plugins/</description></item><item><title>footnotes 2.5.10 reverts 2.5.9d1 and apologies</title><link>https://cheret.org/2021/03/footnotes-2.5.10-reverts-2.5.9d1-and-apologies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 19:02:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cheret.org/2021/03/footnotes-2.5.10-reverts-2.5.9d1-and-apologies/</guid><description>In the development of the WordPress plugin footnotes, we shipped a broken version that crashed websites for arond four hours starting from 08:37 am. Here is the short version. If you want to dive deeper, check out this forum post
Dear footnotes community thank you for your continued support. I’m sorry we shipped a broken version of the plugin earlier today and we reverted to a stable version with the latest update 2.</description></item></channel></rss>