<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>my take - Tag - Mark Cheret - Maker. Artist. Sculptor.</title><link>https://cheret.org/tags/my-take/</link><description>my take - Tag - Mark Cheret - Maker. Artist. Sculptor.</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under the MIT License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2016 21:04:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cheret.org/tags/my-take/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>my take on the Brexit</title><link>https://cheret.org/2016/06/my-take-on-the-brexit/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2016 21:04:11 +0000</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.org/2016/06/my-take-on-the-brexit/</guid><description><![CDATA[In the wake of the recent referendum of the United Kingdom&rsquo;s membership of the European Union which in short was just called &ldquo;Brexit&rdquo; for those in favour of leaving the EU, there has been a lot of buzz online and elsewhere. This of course was to be expected of a vote with the potential of having wide ranging consequences. I&rsquo;d like to call a lot of what&rsquo;s been going on merely &ldquo;noise&rdquo; while trying to distil the essence of it which I&rsquo;d like to call &ldquo;signal&rdquo;.]]></description></item><item><title>my take on "Caprica"</title><link>https://cheret.org/2014/02/my-take-on-caprica/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2014 20:25:59 +0000</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.org/2014/02/my-take-on-caprica/</guid><description><![CDATA[After having recently finished the &ldquo;Reimagined Battlestar Galactica&rdquo; Series (=BSG), it&rsquo;s only logical to carry on watching one of the two prequels that were produced after BSG has aired. These are &ldquo;Battlestar Galactica: Blood &amp; Chrome&rdquo; and &ldquo;Caprica&rdquo;. I decided to watch Caprica first and Blood and Chrome straight after that. As I recently finished watching &ldquo;Caprica&rdquo;, here&rsquo;s my write-up of thoughts on that particular show.
Background information The pilot episode of Caprica is set 58 years before the story of BSG and was released direct to DVD on 21st April 2009.]]></description></item><item><title>my take on "The Reimagined Battlestar Galactica"</title><link>https://cheret.org/2014/01/my-take-on-the-reimagined-battlestar-galactica/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 19:26:49 +0000</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.org/2014/01/my-take-on-the-reimagined-battlestar-galactica/</guid><description>Coming from a perspective of being one of many serious Star Trek fans who have watched absolutely every episode and movie there is out there, presently I can't tell which of these I like better.</description></item><item><title>my take on paper and metal for quenching your thirst for commodities</title><link>https://cheret.org/2013/11/my-take-on-paper-and-metal-for-quenching-your-thirst-for-commodities/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2013 13:01:56 +0000</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.org/2013/11/my-take-on-paper-and-metal-for-quenching-your-thirst-for-commodities/</guid><description>I rarely carry around money , as I believe that money-transfer with paper and metal is way too complicated to be taken seriously. There are all these kinds of problems with exchanging currencies, paying, receiving change (having ready the correct amount of coins), getting your hard earned {insert currency here, i.e. dollars, euros} from your trusted bank to your pocket burns fuel and time, carrying around vast amounts of paper or metal only for the purpose of exchanging CASH for GOODS.</description></item></channel></rss>